PAVEL LONESCU

Blockchain & Fullstack Developer

+40 0722271992

@ www.github.com/maxcore1120

- @ maxcore1120@gmail.com
- Oradea, Romania



SUMMARY

I am a developer with expertise in Blochain and Web Frontend space. I've written and managed smart contract interactions on the Ethereum blockchain, written applications using sbstrate blockchain framworks, built infrustructure, managed complex integrations. I've also designed creative and various kinds of UI/UX which work very well without any issues. And I always get great reviews from the clients, as I accurately & prompetly detect their intention and make good suggestions. I always keep it as my motto to read the relationship with the client in a positive way.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2020 - 2022

Blockchain Developer

Remote, London, UK

- Inlecom
- Led the blockchain integration and development on the CHARIOT Horizon 2020 project, where I developed a
 decentralized PKI cryptographic system.
- Led the blockchain research and innovation aspect on the ICONET Horizon 2020 project, where I developed a purpose-built blockchain for PI logistics using contract arbitration via Ricardian contracts.
- · Worked on several European projects on the proposal stage to meaningfully introduce blockchain technology.
- Contributed to several publications for the aforementioned projects and have presented in major conferences such as IEEE CAMAD 2019.

2019 - 2020

Solidity/Blockchain Expert with Go Experience

Fractal Blockchain

- Contributed to software written in Go which interacts with Ethereum nodes (with geth nodes specifically). Contributed to software written in Go which interacts with Ethereum nodes (with geth nodes specifically).
- Reviewed and improved smart contracts written in Solidity. Curated a \$2M business implementation project that saves ~ \$3.5M on operational inefficiencies between sales and development departments annually Reviewed and improved smart contracts written in Solidity.
- Reviewed and improved software interacting with the Bitcoin network. Collaborated with strategic manufacturing partners to develop an effective onboarding system, reducing the sales cycle by 3 months for global enterprise clientsReviewed and improved software interacting with the Bitcoin network.

2018 - 2019

Full-stack Developer

Remote, Munich, Germany

Remote, Munich, Germany

- DavoscriptReilly GroupDavoscriptGainX
- Developed real-time web applications for SimCase using Node.js and MongoDB to be used by professors and students at the Kellogg School of Management.
- Maintained and designed a database to be shared across multiple games.
- Oversaw the testing and deployment process for the application.

2016 - 2018

Web Developer

Remote, Nandes, France

- **GainX**
- · Provided clients with a seamless development experience from start to finish by combining a knowledge of design best practices and functional programming skills.
- Hosted, deployed, and maintained websites for small businesses using an evolving set of tools and architectures, most recently using predominantly headless CMS coupled with a Next.js/React-based front end deployed to Netlify or Vercel
- Developed an improved workflow for modern WordPress websites for a wide variety of clients in the real estate, retail, and property development spaces.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016

Oradea, Romania

Computer Engineering & Technology
 The Science College in Oradea

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Typescript-React Next.js Vue.js Python Blockchain Smart Contract Solidity Ethereum	Web3
TailwindCss Node/Express.js PHP/Laravel MongoDB Postgre Sql Javascript Html CSS	Git ASP.NET
cPanel AWS Netfily Firebase	